<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollviewDemo</string>
    <string name="text1">Gyalpozhing College of Information Technology</string>
    <string name="text2">Royal University of Bhutan</string>
    <string name="text3">The study examines the influence of social media on academic performance of undergraduate students of Taraba
        state University, Jalingo, Nigeria. Quantitative survey method was adopted for the study. The population consists of 5000 undergraduate students. The study made use of Taro Yames formula to sample 100 students. Questionnaires were employed as the instrument for data collection. The questionnaire was administered to 100 randomly selected students. The entire questionnaires administered were duly filled and retrieved given a high response rate of 100%. The gamut of this study is on the uses and gratification theory. Data collected were coded and analysed on SPSS version 22 and presented in tables. Findings revealed that students of Taraba State University have access to the internet and that they do so through different mediums such as smart phones, tablets and computers. The study also postulate that students who spend more time on social media are likely to perform poorly in their academic activities than those who do not. The study recommends that students should decrease their introduction to social media and give careful consideration to their studies. Students, particularly those ready to record gigantic scholarly achievement should guard themselves against the successive utilization of social media.
    The study examines the influence of social media on academic performance of undergraduate  students  of  Taraba
state University, Jalingo, Nigeria . Quantitative survey method was adopted for the study. The population consists
of  5000  undergraduate  students.  The  study  made  use  of  Taro  Yame’s  formula  to  sample  100  students.
        www.google.com
Questionnaires  were  employed  as  the instrument  for  data collection.  The  questionnaire  was administered  to  100
randomly  selected  students.  The  entire  questionnaires  administered  were  duly  filled  and  retrieved  given a  high
response rate  of 100%. The gamut of this  study is on the uses and  gratification theory. Data collected were coded
and  analysed  on  SPSS  version  22  and  presented  in  tables.  Findings  revealed  that  students  of  Taraba  State
University have access to the internet and that they do so through different mediums such as smart phones, tablets
and computers.  The study also postulate that students who spend more time on social  media are likely to perform
poorly  in  their  academic activities than  those  who  do  not.  The  study recommends  that  students  should  decrease
their introduction to social media and give careful consideration to their studies. Students, particularly those ready
to record gigantic scholarly achievement should guard themselves against the successive utilization of social media.  </string>

</resources>